tf3dm.com 2019-06-30

# Free3D - About us

We ask you for certain personal information (“Personal Data”) as part of the application process. The type of information we require is the minimum necessary for Free3D to provide our visitors and members through the Free3D website (the “Site”). Before you create an account with Free3D, we ask that you read and accept this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to the Free3D Site, Free3D’s processes, and communications to third parties. 

Free3D values and respects your privacy, therefore, it is our policy and practice to keep your Personal Data strictly confidential at all times particularly as regards the collection, use, retention, transfer, disclosure, security, and access of Personal Data. By consenting to this Privacy Policy, you expressly and unconditionally agree to our use of and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described within it.

We provide that only your visits to Free3D will be recorded; we will not keep records of information that personally identifies you or anything about you. A component of our Privacy Policy dictates that if any Cookies* are used in any part of the Site, they will not be programmed for collecting your personal information.

We use SSL and encryption practices designed to protect your privacy; however, we cannot and do not guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. Although we take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage are completely secure. Therefore, while we make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

There may be instances in which you will be asked to provide us with your personal information including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone or fax number, email address, credit card information, age, gender, education level, occupation, or other specific information. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be able to gain access to specific parts of the Site; or we may not be able to process certain requests or applications on your behalf. Depending on the reason for your visit to our Site, failure to produce certain personal information may prevent you from using our Site to your best advantage.

Free3D often hosts service providers or online stores operated by third-party merchants. Once we transfer any of your personal information to such service providers or online stores in the facilitation of your order(s) for services or products, your personal information is out of our control, and therefore outside the scope of our protection, as provided in this Privacy Policy. 

When you provide Free3D with your personal information, you are allowing us to use that information for the following purposes, in addition to any other purposes as required by law and/or agreed to between you and Free3D:

  1. Service Provisioning
  2. Marketing of the services and/or products by Free3D, its agents or subsidiaries   

  3. Review and verification of your credit, payment, or customer status as it relates to service provisioning   

  4. Processing of any payment directions, and/or debit/credit card information at your request   

  5. Enabling and maintaining your daily account operation and/or the collection of any outstanding balance(s) of your account as it relates to the Service Provisioning
  6. Processing of any benefits that have resulted from or that are connected to Service Provisioning 

In addition to the above-mentioned purposes, you must accept the disclosure and transfer of your personal information by Free3D to any third party service providers, banks, financial institutions, credit providers, credit reference agencies, collection agencies, and security agencies; in addition to Free3D agents, contractors, professional advisers, and any other persons under a duty of confidentiality to Free3D and any of our actual or proposed assignees or transferees of our rights of processing, using, disclosing, retaining, holding, or transferring such Personal Data. 

Free3D reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Free3D.

* You may choose not to accept Cookies by resetting the relevant options of your Internet browser. However, please note that you may not then be able to enable or optimize the use of specific functions made available through the Free3D Site.
